ifone.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy - glu mobile | Download mobile java games | Download cell phone games

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you are visiting this Website, you indicate your agreement to our use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. The term 'personal information' refers to information which identifies, or is capable of identifying, you as an individual.**

This Privacy Policy covers the iFone Service (see [Terms and Conditions](http://www.ifone.com/terms)) and this website only. Please be aware that iFone cannot be held responsible for the privacy of any information which you provide to any website operated by a third party accessed via a link from iFone's Website. In such cases, the privacy policy of such third party website shall apply.

If you decide to download a Java game using the iFone Service, we will ask you for relevant information to ensure we fulfil your orders as swiftly as possible. We may also ask you for other optional information. We may also ask you for personal information if you enter into one of the competitions or promotions on our website or if you wish to access any chatroom facility we may offer. We will also ask you to confirm whether or not you would like us to contact you with information which iFone thinks may be of interest to you, which may include information from selected third parties. If you agree to receive information about other companies' products or services, we will only share your personal information with those companies if they agree to use your personal information only for that purpose.

The information we collect is used by us to:

  * confirm our acceptance of your desire to download a Java game via the iFone Service
  * communicate with you about the iFone Service
  * market new iFone products or third party products and services, subject to the choices you make about this

We may sometimes ask other companies to provide any of the above services on our behalf and if we do this we will share your personal information with them for this purpose. These companies can only process this information according to the instructions we give them. 

During the course of your visit to this Website we also collect various anonymous information relating to your use of this Website, including your internet address and information relating to the type and version of your internet browser. iFone collects this information to allow us to monitor your use of this Website, to personalise the content of this Website to your preferences and, when aggregated with information collected from other users, so that iFone can improve the quality of this Website.

iFone may use 'cookies' to enhance your enjoyment of the Website. If your browser permits it, you may set your computer to reject iFone's cookies although this may affect the quality of your visit to this Website.

If you wish to check the details iFone holds about you, you should contact [The iFone Webmaster](http://www.ifone.com/contact) as set out in the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.ifone.com/terms). An official fee will be payable.

If you believe that any of the information iFone holds about you to be incorrect or incomplete, please notify us by contacting [The iFone Webmaster](http://www.ifone.com/contact) as set out in the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.ifone.com/terms). Any information discovered to be incorrect or incomplete will be updated as soon as possible following iFone's receipt of notification.
